const quizData = [{
        question: "What does JSON stand for?",
        opt: [
            "JavaScript Object Name",
            "JavaScript Object Numeric",
            "JavaScript Oriented Notation",
            "JavaScript Object Notation"
        ],
        answer: "JavaScript Object Notation",
    },
    {
        question: "Which type of JavaScript language is ___",
        opt: [
            "Object-Oriented",
            "Object-Based",
            "Assembly-language",
            "High-level"
        ],
        answer: "Object-Based",
    },
    {
        question: "In JavaScript the x===y statement implies that:",
        opt: [
            "Both x and y are equal in value, type and reference address as well.",
            "Both are x and y are equal in value only.",
            "Both are equal in the value and data type.",
            "Both are not same at all."
        ],
        answer: "Both are equal in the value and data type.",
    },
    {
        question: "Which one of the following also known as Conditional Expression",
        opt: [
            "Alternative to if-else",
            "Swtich statement",
            "if-then-else statement",
            "immediate if"
        ],
        answer: "immediate if",
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following variables takes precedence over the others if the names are the same?",
        opt: [
            "Global variable",
            "The local element",
            "The two of the above",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        answer: "The local element",
    },
    {
        question: "The correct sequence of HTML tags for starting a webpage is",
        opt: [
            "Head, Title, HTML, body",
            "HTML, Body, Title, Head",
            "HTML, Head, Title, Body",
            "HTML, Head, Title, Body"
        ],
        answer: "HTML, Head, Title, Body",
    },
    {
        question: "The CSS property used to control the element's font-size is -",
        opt: [
            "text-style",
            "text-size",
            "font-size",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        answer: "font-size",
    },
    {
        question: "jQuery is a -",
        opt: [
            "JavaScript method",
            "JavaScript library",
            "JSON library",
            "PHP method"
        ],
        answer: "JavaScript library",
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following jQuery method is used to hide the selected elements?",
        opt: [
            "The hidden method",
            "The hide method",
            "The visible -false- method",
            "The display -none- method"
        ],
        answer: "The hide method",
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following jQuery method is used to attach a handler to an event?",
        opt: [
            "unbind method",
            "attach method",
            "bind method",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        answer: "attach method",
    },
    {
        "question": "Which method of the Class.class is used to determine the name of a class represented by the class object as a String?",
        "opt": [
            "getClass",
            "intern",
            "getName",
            "toString"
        ],
        answer: "getName",
    },
    {
        question: "An HTML program is saved by using the ____ extension.",
        opt: [
            ".ht",
            ".html",
            ".hml",
            "one of the above"
        ],
        answer: ".html",
    }
];